https://www.olts-bt.com/about-us/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy - Outdoor Leadership Training Seminars
Skip to content
Menu HomeOutdoor CoursesBreaking Through AdventuresCanyon QuestDeep EcologyTherapeutic WildernessWeaving the WebOutdoor Leadership Training5 Month SeminarFall SeminarSummer IntensiveWilderness LeadershipOutdoor Skills TrainingAlpine Mountaineering TrainingCentered Climbing WorkshopsOutdoor Adventure CoursesWhitewater RaftingArticlesCapturing the Peak ExperienceThe Centered ClimberThe Tao of SkiingCorporate TrainingAbout UsOutdoor Jobs at OLTS FacebookLinkedinInstagramContact Us303-320-0372
Menu
HomeOutdoor CoursesBreaking Through AdventuresCanyon QuestDeep EcologyTherapeutic WildernessWeaving the WebOutdoor Leadership Training5 Month SeminarFall SeminarSummer IntensiveWilderness LeadershipOutdoor Skills TrainingAlpine Mountaineering TrainingCentered Climbing WorkshopsOutdoor Adventure CoursesWhitewater RaftingArticlesCapturing the Peak ExperienceThe Centered ClimberThe Tao of SkiingCorporate TrainingAbout UsOutdoor Jobs at OLTSHome » About Us » Privacy Policy Privacy PolicyWHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECTOLTS (Outdoor Leadership Training Seminars) is committed to securing any of your data that we collect online and to only collecting what we need to serve our community and customers.This policy is designed so that you understand what information is collected by OLTS when you visit our website, what we do with that data, and how you can review/correct your data.PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION (PII)By simply browsing our website we collect very little data about you as a person. We do automatically collect information about how you use the website so that we can make it better and improve the user experience. For example: to make our pages flow in the most logical way possible and making the web site faster to load the pages.If you are applying for a OLTS course through the OLTS website, we request your basic contact details or require that you create an account to access specific content related to your requests. If you are downloading content from our site, signing up for a newsletter, or requesting more information from us, we will prompt you to enter additional information such as first and last name, email address, address, and phone number so that we can best address your requests for information.We share this type of information within OLTS to use as part of our everyday business practices, such as processing your requested transactions, maintaining your account, and responding to court orders and legal investigations. We also share information within OLTS so that we can offer relevant products, benefits, and services to you.When you are no longer an active customer, we may continue to share your information internally as described in this notice.OLTS does not sell your information to external companies and only shares with key third party partners to leverage their services on your behalf.  You can see more about our use of third party services below.COOKIESLike most websites, the OLTS website uses cookies to collect information. Cookies are small data files which are placed on your computer or other devices (such as smartphones or tablets) as you browse this website. They are used to “remember” when your computer or device accesses our websites. Cookies are essential for the effective operation of our websites and helping you interact with us online.We may use cookies to determine whether you have visited our site previously and to save and remember any preferences that you set while using our site. Cookies also allow us to measure activity on our site and to improve your user experience.THIRD PARTY SERVICESOLTS does not sell your information to third parties; however, we do share some information with a limited number of third party companies performing services on our behalf. These services include things such as marketing, website analytics, and payment services. These companies are prohibited from using your personal information for purposes other than those requested by us or required by law.PAYMENT SERVICESOLTS accepts payments in a number of ways.  This section specifically deals with the electronic payments we accept through our website.  OLTS does not store credit card or bank account information.Credit Card PaymentsOLTS uses Stripe, Inc. (Stripe) or PayPal to allow our visitors to submit online payments with their credit card. For more information, please see the Stripe privacy policy and PayPal privacy policy.TRANSFER AND PROCESSING OF DATAOLTS is headquartered in Denver, Colorado, United States of America and our websites are also hosted in the United States of America. Any personal information submitted to OLTS will be transferred from your computer to the OLTS database (also in the United States of America) where it will be stored. By providing your personal information you are expressly consenting to this transfer, processing, and use of this data. In some instances you could be submitting information via one of our trusted partners, such as MailChimp.ACCESS TO YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATIONTo request a copy of your information please send your request via email using our contact form or via mail to OLTS P.O. Box 200281, Denver, CO 80220.CORRECTING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATIONYou may modify your personal information, address, phone number, and email via the OLTS website in some cases.You may also request a correction to your information via email or mail. For email, please send your request via email using our contact form. For mail submissions please send requests to OLTS P.O. Box 200281, Denver, CO 80220. We reserve the right to maintain certain information for record keeping purposes and/or to complete any transactions that are in progress.CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICYThis policy undergoes periodic internal review and will be updated on our website when any changes are made. This policy was last updated on May 19, 2019. NavigateOutdoor CoursesCorporate TrainingArticlesAbout UsContact UsOutdoor Leadership Training Seminars303-320-0372P.O. Box 200281, Denver, CO 80220Connect With Us Facebook
LinkedIn
Instagram
Notices: *Outdoor Leadership Training operates under a special use permit from the USDA Forest Service, San Carlos Ranger District.
Copyright © Outdoor Leadership Training Seminars 1973-2020 Web Design and Development by ON2kSite MapTermsPrivacy Policy Scroll To Top
